Guide to the Goodwin J. (Goodwin Jess) Knight Papers, 1896-1988 (inclusive), 1946-1970 (bulk)
Department of Special Collections
- Series 1. Correspondence
  - Subseries 3. Correspondence
    - 1960 November December1960 November December, Accession no. M0245 (Box 10, Folder 108)
    - General undated correspondence l960, Accession no. M0245 (Box 10, Folder 109)
    - "Support Goldwater", Accession no. M0245 (Box 10, Folder 110)
    - Education, Accession no. M0245 (Box 10, Folder 111)
    - Operation Abolition" - Americanism, Accession no. M0245 (Box 10, Folder 111)
    - 1961 January 1 - 17, Accession no. M0245 (Box 11, Folder 112)
    - 1961 January 18-25, Accession no. M0245 (Box 11, Folder 113)
    - 1961 January 26 - 31, Accession no. M0245 (Box 11, Folder 114)
    - 1961 February 1 - 17, Accession no. M0245 (Box 11, Folder 115)
    - 1961 February 17 - 28, Accession no. M0245 (Box 11, Folder 116)
    - 1961 March 1 - 16, Accession no. M0245 (Box 11, Folder 117)
    - 1961 March 17 - 31, Accession no. M0245 (Box 11, Folder 113)
    - 1961 April 1 - 11, Accession no. M0245 (Box 12, Folder 119)
    - 1961 April 12 - 31, Accession no. M0245 (Box 12, Folder 120)
    - 1961 May 1~-- 19, Accession no. M0245 (Box 12, Folder 121)
    - 1961 May 19 - 31, Accession no. M0245 (Box 12, Folder 122)
    - 1961 June, Accession no. M0245 (Box 12, Folder 123)
    - 1961 July, Accession no. M0245 (Box 13, Folder 124)
    - 1961 August, Accession no. M0245 (Box 13, Folder 125)
    - 1961 September l-12, Accession no. M0245 (Box 13, Folder 126)
    - 1961 September 13 - 20, Accession no. M0245 (Box 13, Folder 127)
    - 1961 September 20 - 30, Accession no. M0245 (Box 13, Folder 123)
    - 1961 September 20 - 30, Accession no. M0245 (Box 13, Folder 129)
    - 1961 October 1- 51961 Oct 1 - 1961 Oct 5, Accession no. M0245 (Box 14, Folder 129)
    - 1961 October 6- 161961 Oct 6 - 1961 Oct 16, Accession no. M0245 (Box 14, Folder 130)
    - 1961 October 16 - 311961 Oct16 - 1961 Oct 31, Accession no. M0245 (Box 14, Folder 131)
    - 1961 November1961 Nov, Accession no. M0245 (Box 14, Folder 132)
    - 1961 December1961 Dec, Accession no. M0245 (Box 15, Folder 133)
    - Invitations 1961 Jan - 1961 August, Accession no. M0245 (Box 15, Folder 134)
    - 1961 Sept, Accession no. M0245 (Box 15, Folder 135)
    - Invitations 1961 Oct - 1961 Dec, Accession no. M0245 (Box 15, Folder 136)
    - Volunteers - Contributions1961, Accession no. M0245 (Box 15, Folder 137)
    - Form letters1961, Accession no. M0245 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Undated correspondence1961, Accession no. M0245 (Box 15, Folder 138)
    - Undated correspondence1961, Accession no. M0245 (Box 15, Folder 139)
    - 1962 January - February1962 Jan - 1962 Feb, Accession no. M0245 (Box 16, Folder 140)
    - March - Desember1962, Accession no. M0245 (Box 16, Folder 141)
    - January - February1963, Accession no. M0245 (Box 16, Folder 142)
    - March - May1963, Accession no. M0245 (Box 16, Folder 143)
    - June - August1963, Accession no. M0245 (Box 16, Folder 144)
    - September - December1963, Accession no. M0245 (Box 16, Folder 145)
    - 19641964, Accession no. M0245 (Box 17, Folder 146)
    - January - May1965, Accession no. M0245 (Box 17, Folder 147)
    - June - August1965, Accession no. M0245 (Box 17, Folder 148)
    - September December1965, Accession no. M0245 (Box 17, Folder 149)
    - Ettie Lee1965, Accession no. M0245 (Box 17, Folder 150)
    - 1966 January - September, Accession no. M0245 (Box 18, Folder 151)
    - 1966 October - December, Accession no. M0245 (Box 18, Folder 151)
    - 1967, Accession no. M0245 (Box 18, Folder 152)
    - 1967 January - June 301967 Jan - 1967 June 30, Accession no. M0245 (Box 18, Folder 153)
    - 19681968, Accession no. M0245 (Box 18, Folder 154)
    - Personal1968, Accession no. M0245 (Box 18, Folder 155)
    - 1969, Accession no. M0245 (Box 18, Folder 156)
    - 1966 - 1971, Accession no. M0245 (Box 19, Folder 157)
    - Cadillac, Accession no. M0245 (Box 19, Folder 157)
    - Political Material (post-1961fl), Accession no. M0245 (Box 19, Folder 158)
    - Undated, Accession no. M0245 (Box 19, Folder 58)
    - Notes, miscellaneous, Accession no. M0245 (Box 19, Folder 158)
    - Americanism, Accession no. M0245 (Box 23, Folder 209)
    - Biographies, Accession no. M0245 (Box 23, Folder 209)
    - Budget - general, Accession no. M0245 (Box 23, Folder 209)
    - Calhoun, Alice, Accession no. M0245 (Box 23, Folder 211)
    - California Republican Convention, Accession no. M0245 (Box 23, Folder 212)
    - Canpaign Expenditures 1954, Accession no. M0245 (Box 23, Folder 213)
    - Cancer Prevention, Accession no. M0245 (Box 23, Folder 314)
    - City of Hope, Accession no. M0245 (Box 23, Folder 215)
    - Civil Defense, Accession no. M0245 (Box 23, Folder 216)
    - Eation Marilyn and Robert, Accession no. M0245 (Box 23, Folder 217)
    - Ettie Lee, Accession no. M0245 (Box 23, Folder 218)
    - Fraternity, Accession no. M0245 (Box 23, Folder 219)
    - Freeways, Accession no. M0245 (Box 23, Folder 220)
    - Greece, Accession no. M0245 (Box 23, Folder 221)
    - Judgeship Petitions, Accession no. M0245 (Box 23, Folder 222)
    - Knight, Carolyn - wedding, Accession no. M0245 (Box 23, Folder 223)
    - Knight, Carolyn, Accession no. M0245 (Box 23, Folder 224)
    - Governor Knight's Stand, Accession no. M0245 (Box 23, Folder 225)
    - Law Day, Accession no. M0245 (Box 23, Folder 226)
    - Los Angeles, Accession no. M0245 (Box 23, Folder 227)
    - Payroll - Lt. Governor, Accession no. M0245 (Box 23, Folder 228)
    - Religious material, Accession no. M0245 (Box 24, Folder 229)
    - Richmond - San Refal Bridge, Accession no. M0245 (Box 24, Folder 229)
    - Republican National Convention, Accession no. M0245 (Box 24, Folder 230)
    - San Francisco, Accession no. M0245 (Box 24, Folder 231)
    - Statements of Vote - Election results, Accession no. M0245 (Box 24, Folder 232)
    - Todt, George, Accession no. M0245 (Box 24, Folder 233)
    - Tournament of Roses, Accession no. M0245 (Box 24, Folder 234)
    - United Nations, Accession no. M0245 (Box 24, Folder 235)
    - University of California, Accession no. M0245 (Box 24, Folder 236)
    - Veterans - Clippings, Accession no. M0245 (Box 24, Folder 237)
    - Veterans - Plaques, awards, etc., Accession no. M0245 (Box 24, Folder 238)
    - Water, Accession no. M0245 (Box 24, Folder 239)
    - Water, Accession no. M0245 (Box 24, Folder 240)
    - Aa-Ak, Accession no. M0245 (Box 25, Folder 241)
    - Al-Am, Accession no. M0245 (Box 25, Folder 242)
    - An-Ar, Accession no. M0245 (Box 25, Folder 243)
    - As-Az., Accession no. M0245 (Box 25, Folder 244)
    - Ba-Baq, Accession no. M0245 (Box 25, Folder 245)
    - Bar, Accession no. M0245 (Box 25, Folder 246)
    - Bas-Bd, Accession no. M0245 (Box 26, Folder 247)
    - Be-Bh, Accession no. M0245 (Box 26, Folder 248)
    - Bi-Bk, Accession no. M0245 (Box 26, Folder 249)
    - Bl-Bn, Accession no. M0245 (Box 26, Folder 250)
    - Bo-Bq, Accession no. M0245 (Box 26, Folder 251)
    - Bra-Brd, Accession no. M0245 (Box 26, Folder 252)
    - Bre-Brn, Accession no. M0245 (Box 26, Folder 253)
    - Bro-Bt, Accession no. M0245 (Box 27, Folder 254)
    - Bu-Bz, Accession no. M0245 (Box 27, Folder 255)
    - Ca-Caq, Accession no. M0245 (Box 27, Folder 256)
    - Carlson, Accession no. M0245 (Box 27, Folder 257)
    - Car-Cd, Accession no. M0245 (Box 27, Folder 258)
    - Ce-Ch, Accession no. M0245 (Box 28, Folder 259)
    - Ci-Cn, Accession no. M0245 (Box 28, Folder 260)
    - Coa-Col, Accession no. M0245 (Box 28, Folder 261)
    - Com-Coo, Accession no. M0245 (Box 28, Folder 262)
    - Coq-Cq, Accession no. M0245 (Box 28, Folder 263)
    - Cr-Ct, Accession no. M0245 (Box 29, Folder 264)
    - Cu, Accession no. M0245 (Box 29, Folder 265)
    - Damgard, Mr. and Mrs. John, Accession no. M0245 (Box 29, Folder 266)
    - Davis (A-Z), Accession no. M0245 (Box 29, Folder 267)
    - Da-Dd, Accession no. M0245 (Box 29, Folder 268)
    - De-Dh, Accession no. M0245 (Box 29, Folder 269)
    - Di-Dom, Accession no. M0245 (Box 30, Folder 270)
    - Don-Dt, Accession no. M0245 (Box 30, Folder 271)
    - Du-Dz, Accession no. M0245 (Box 30, Folder 272)
    - Ea-Ek, Accession no. M0245 (Box 30, Folder 273)
    - El-Eq, Accession no. M0245 (Box 30, Folder 274)
    - Er-Ez, Accession no. M0245 (Box 30, Folder 275)
    - Fa-Fh, Accession no. M0245 (Box 30, Folder 276)
    - Fi-Fn, Accession no. M0245 (Box 31, Folder 277)
    - Flynn, Patrick and Maria, Accession no. M0245 (Box 31, Folder 278)
    - Fo-Ft, Accession no. M0245 (Box 31, Folder 279)
    - Fu-Fz, Accession no. M0245 (Box 31, Folder 280)
    - Ga-Gd, Accession no. M0245 (Box 31, Folder 281)
    - Ge-Gh, Accession no. M0245 (Box 31, Folder 282)
    - Gi-Gn, Accession no. M0245 (Box 31, Folder 283)
    - Go-Gq, Accession no. M0245 (Box 32, Folder 284)
    - Gr-Gt, Accession no. M0245 (Box 32, Folder 285)
    - Gu-Gz, Accession no. M0245 (Box 32, Folder 286)
    - Haa-Ham, Accession no. M0245 (Box 32, Folder 287)
    - Han-liar, Accession no. M0245 (Box 32, Folder 288)
    - Ha-Hd, Accession no. M0245 (Box 33, Folder 289)
    - Hea-Hem, Accession no. M0245 (Box 33, Folder 290)
    - Hen-It, Accession no. M0245 (Box 33, Folder 291)
    - Hi-Hn, Accession no. M0245 (Box 33, Folder 292)
    - Hoa-Hom, Accession no. M0245 (Box 33, Folder 293)
    - Hon-Ht, Accession no. M0245 (Box 33, Folder 294)
    - Hu-Hz, Accession no. M0245 (Box 34, Folder 295)
    - I, Accession no. M0245 (Box 34, Folder 296)
    - Ja-Jn, Accession no. M0245 (Box 34, Folder 297)
    - Jo-Jz, Accession no. M0245 (Box 34, Folder 298)
    - Ka-Kd, Accession no. M0245 (Box 34, Folder 299)
    - Ke-Kb., Accession no. M0245 (Box 35, Folder 300)
    - Keck, Win. M., Accession no. M0245 (Box 35, Folder 301)
    - Ki-Kk, Accession no. M0245 (Box 35, Folder 302)
    - K1-Kt, Accession no. M0245 (Box 35, Folder 303)
    - Ku-Kz, Accession no. M0245 (Box 35, Folder 304)
    - La-taq, Accession no. M0245 (Box 35, Folder 305)
    - Land Family, Accession no. M0245 (Box 36, Folder 306)
    - Lar-Ld, Accession no. M0245 (Box 36, Folder 307)
    - Lea-Lem, Accession no. M0245 (Box 36, Folder 308)
    - Len-Lh, Accession no. M0245 (Box 36, Folder 309)
    - Li-Ln, Accession no. M0245 (Box 36, Folder 310)
    - Lo-Lz, Accession no. M0245 (Box 36, Folder 311)
    - Maa-Mao, Accession no. M0245 (Box 37, Folder 312)
    - Map-Mb, Accession no. M0245 (Box 37, Folder 313)
    - McA-McC, Accession no. M0245 (Box 37, Folder 314)
    - McD-McG, Accession no. M0245 (Box 37, Folder 315)
    - McH-McM, Accession no. M0245 (Box 38, Folder 316)
    - McN-McZ, Accession no. M0245 (Box 38, Folder 317)
    - Me-It, Accession no. M0245 (Box 38, Folder 318)
    - Mi-Mn, Accession no. M0245 (Box 38, Folder 319)
    - Mo-Mt, Accession no. M0245 (Box 39, Folder 320)
    - Mu-Mz, Accession no. M0245 (Box 39, Folder 321)
    - Na-Nh, Accession no. M0245 (Box 39, Folder 322)
    - Ni-Nt, Accession no. M0245 (Box 40, Folder 323)
    - North, Accession no. M0245 (Box 40, Folder 324)
    - Nu-Nz, Accession no. M0245 (Box 40, Folder 325)
    - Oa-Ok, Accession no. M0245 (Box 40, Folder 326)
    - Okita Letter, Accession no. M0245 (Box 40, Folder 327)
    - Ol-Oz, Accession no. M0245 (Box 40, Folder 328)
    - Pa-Pap, Accession no. M0245 (Box 40, Folder 329)
    - Par-Pd, Accession no. M0245 (Box 41, Folder 330)
    - Pe-Pg, Accession no. M0245 (Box 41, Folder 331)
    - Ph, Accession no. M0245 (Box 41, Folder 332)
    - Pi-Pk, Accession no. M0245 (Box 42, Folder 333)
    - Pierce, Mon, Accession no. M0245 (Box 42, Folder 334)
    - Pl-Pq, Accession no. M0245 (Box 42, Folder 335)
    - Pr-Pt, Accession no. M0245 (Box 42, Folder 336)
    - Puerto Rico 1957, Accession no. M0245 (Box 42, Folder 337)
    - Pu-Pz, Accession no. M0245 (Box 42, Folder 338)
    - Q, Accession no. M0245 (Box 42, Folder 339)
    - Ba-Rd, Accession no. M0245 (Box 42, Folder 340)
    - Re-Rh, Accession no. M0245 (Box 42, Folder 341)
    - Relatives of VK, Accession no. M0245 (Box 43, Folder 342)
    - Ri-Rn, Accession no. M0245 (Box 43, Folder 343)
    - Ro-Rof, Accession no. M0245 (Box 43, Folder 344)
    - Rog-Rt, Accession no. M0245 (Box 43, Folder 345)
    - Ru-Rz, Accession no. M0245 (Box 43, Folder 346)
    - Sa-Sb, Accession no. M0245 (Box 43, Folder 347)
    - Salvation Army, Accession no. M0245 (Box 44, Folder 348)
    - Sca-Sch, Accession no. M0245 (Box 44, Folder 349)
    - Schmidt, Frank, Accession no. M0245 (Box 44, Folder 350)
    - Sci-Sd, Accession no. M0245 (Box 44, Folder 351)
    - Sé-Sg, Accession no. M0245 (Box 44, Folder 352)
    - Sha-Shh, Accession no. M0245 (Box 44, Folder 353)
    - Shi-Shz, Accession no. M0245 (Box 44, Folder 354)
    - Si-Smh, Accession no. M0245 (Box 44, Folder 355)
    - Smi-Smz, Accession no. M0245 (Box 45, Folder 356)
    - Smith, Accession no. M0245 (Box 45, Folder 357)
    - Sn-So, Accession no. M0245 (Box 45, Folder 358)
    - Sp-Ss, Accession no. M0245 (Box 45, Folder 359)
    - Sta-Sth, Accession no. M0245 (Box 45, Folder 360)
    - Sti-Stz, Accession no. M0245 (Box 45, Folder 361)
    - Su-Sz, Accession no. M0245 (Box 45, Folder 362)
    - Ta-Tg, Accession no. M0245 (Box 46, Folder 363)
    - Th-Tq, Accession no. M0245 (Box 46, Folder 364)
    - Tibbitts, Accession no. M0245 (Box 46, Folder 365)
    - Tr-Tz, Accession no. M0245 (Box 46, Folder 366)
    - U, Accession no. M0245 (Box 46, Folder 367)
    - V, Accession no. M0245 (Box 46, Folder 368)
    - Waa-Wal, Accession no. M0245 (Box 47, Folder 369)
    - Wam-Yd, Accession no. M0245 (Box 47, Folder 370)
    - We-Wg, Accession no. M0245 (Box 47, Folder 371)
    - Wh, Accession no. M0245 (Box 47, Folder 372)
    - Whitaker and Baxter, Accession no. M0245 (Box 47, Folder 373)
    - Wia-Wik, Accession no. M0245 (Box 47, Folder 374)
    - Wil-Wilr, Accession no. M0245 (Box 48, Folder 375)
    - Wim-Wn, Accession no. M0245 (Box 48, Folder 376)
    - Wo-Wz, Accession no. M0245 (Box 48, Folder 377)
    - Women's Organizations, Accession no. M0245 (Box 48, Folder 378)
    - X-Y, Accession no. M0245 (Box 48, Folder 379)
    - Z, Accession no. M0245 (Box 48, Folder 380)
    - Aniversary Forms, Accession no. M0245 (Box 49, Folder 381)
    - Baby Congratulations, Accession no. M0245 (Box 49, Folder 382)
    - Birthday Greetings, Accession no. M0245 (Box 49, Folder 383)
    - Birthday Greetings Cards, Accession no. M0245 (Box 49, Folder 384)
    - Birthday Thank You s, Accession no. M0245 (Box 49, Folder 385)
    - "Bright Dawn" letter 3-58, Accession no. M0245 (Box 49, Folder 386)
    - Campaign, Accession no. M0245 (Box 49, Folder 387)
    - " Inaugural Dinner USS 2-24-58., Accession no. M0245 (Box 49, Folder 388)
    - Christmas 1958 Thank You 5, Accession no. M0245 (Box 49, Folder 389)
    - "Christmas 1957 Thank yous s Gifts (from Gov.), Accession no. M0245 (Box 49, Folder 390)
    - Clippings Thank You s, Accession no. M0245 (Box 49, Folder 391)
    - Contribution Requests, Accession no. M0245 (Box 49, Folder 392)
    - Condolence Forms, Accession no. M0245 (Box 49, Folder 393)
    - Condolence and Convalescent, Accession no. M0245 (Box 49, Folder 394)
    - Engagement Congratulations, Accession no. M0245 (Box 49, Folder 395)
    - Fiesta del Pacifico, Accession no. M0245 (Box 49, Folder 396)
    - Flower Thank You s, Accession no. M0245 (Box 49, Folder 397)
    - Friendship Thank You s, Accession no. M0245 (Box 49, Folder 398)
    - Get Well Letters, Accession no. M0245 (Box 49, Folder 399)
    - Get Well Thank You s, Accession no. M0245 (Box 49, Folder 400)
    - Graduation', Accession no. M0245 (Box 49, Folder 401)
    - Greeting Card Thank You s, Accession no. M0245 (Box 49, Folder 402)
    - Governor's Birthday 1957, Accession no. M0245 (Box 49, Folder 403)
    - Gift Sheets 1953, Accession no. M0245 (Box 49, Folder 404)
    - Gift Sheets 1957, Accession no. M0245 (Box 49, Folder 405)
    - Governor's Biography, Accession no. M0245 (Box 50, Folder 406)
    - Governor's Thank You s, Accession no. M0245 (Box 50, Folder 407)
    - Governor's Conference 1958, Accession no. M0245 (Box 50, Folder 408)
    - Governor's Conference 1957, Accession no. M0245 (Box 50, Folder 409)
    - Governor's Conference (Western) 1958, Accession no. M0245 (Box 50, Folder 410)
    - Holiday Statements, Accession no. M0245 (Box 50, Folder 411)
    - Honorary Memberships, Accession no. M0245 (Box 50, Folder 412)
    - Hostess (Mansion), Accession no. M0245 (Box 50, Folder 413)
    - InvitatIons Acceptend, Accession no. M0245 (Box 50, Folder 414)
    - Invitations Declined, Accession no. M0245 (Box 50, Folder 415)
    - Mansion, Information re:, Accession no. M0245 (Box 50, Folder 416)
    - Occasion Thank You Form, Accession no. M0245 (Box 50, Folder 417)
    - Open House 1958, Accession no. M0245 (Box 50, Folder 418)
    - Other Poems, Accession no. M0245 (Box 50, Folder 419)
    - Photographers, Accession no. M0245 (Box 50, Folder 420)
    - Picture Thank You s, Accession no. M0245 (Box 50, Folder 421)
    - Poems Published and Offers, Accession no. M0245 (Box 50, Folder 422)
    - Poetry from others, Accession no. M0245 (Box 50, Folder 423)
    - Poets and Poetry Tkakk You s, Accession no. M0245 (Box 50, Folder 424)
    - Political Support, Accession no. M0245 (Box 50, Folder 425)
    - Political Paragraphs, Accession no. M0245 (Box 51, Folder 426)
    - Recipe Requests, Accession no. M0245 (Box 51, Folder 427)
    - Reporters, Accession no. M0245 (Box 51, Folder 428)
    - Republican, Accession no. M0245 (Box 51, Folder 429)
    - Reprint copies (poems and recipes), Accession no. M0245 (Box 51, Folder 430)
    - Thank You letters for gifts, Accession no. M0245 (Box 51, Folder 431)
    - "Virginia", Accession no. M0245 (Box 51, Folder 432)
    - Wedding Congratulations Form, Accession no. M0245 (Box 51, Folder 433)
    - Women's Club, Accession no. M0245 (Box 51, Folder 434)
    - Samples, Accession no. M0245 (Box 51, Folder 435)
    - Samples, Accession no. M0245 (Box 52)
    - Schedules, Accession no. M0245 (Box 53)
  - Subseries 4. Personality Files
    This subseries describes materials from a latter aquisition (M0245) that have now been incorporated into the Goodwin Knight Papers (M0244). Prior to its incorporation into M0244 this subseries was listed as Subseries 2. Personality Files in M0245
    - A-B, Accession no. M0245 (Box 20, Folder 159)
    - Alderman, Accession no. M0245 (Box 20, Folder 160)
    - Alioto, Accession no. M0245 (Box 20, Folder 161)
    - Bonelli, Accession no. M0245 (Box 20, Folder 162)
    - Brown, Accession no. M0245 (Box 20, Folder 163)
    - Button, Accession no. M0245 (Box 20, Folder 164)
    - C-D, Accession no. M0245 (Box 20, Folder 165)
    - Christopher, Accession no. M0245 (Box 20, Folder 166)
    - Dewey, Accession no. M0245 (Box 20, Folder 167)
    - E-F-G, Accession no. M0245 (Box 20, Folder 168)
    - Eisenhower, Accession no. M0245 (Box 20, Folder 169)
    - Flournoy, Accession no. M0245 (Box 20, Folder 170)
    - deForest, Accession no. M0245 (Box 20, Folder 171)
    - Goldwater, Accession no. M0245 (Box 20, Folder 172)
    - Graham, Accession no. M0245 (Box 20, Folder 173)
    - Graves, Accession no. M0245 (Box 20, Folder 174)
    - H-I-J, Accession no. M0245 (Box 20, Folder 175)
    - Hershberger, Accession no. M0245 (Box 20, Folder 176)
    - Jessel, Accession no. M0245 (Box 20, Folder 177)
    - Jordan, Accession no. M0245 (Box 20, Folder 178)
    - K-L, Accession no. M0245 (Box 20, Folder 179)
    - Knight biographical material, Accession no. M0245 (Box 20, Folder 180)
    - Knight biographical material, Accession no. M0245 (Box 20, Folder 181)
    - Knowland, Accession no. M0245 (Box 20, Folder 182)
    - Kuchel, Accession no. M0245 (Box 20, Folder 183)
    - M-N-O, Accession no. M0245 (Box 20, Folder 184)
    - MacArthur, Accession no. M0245 (Box 21, Folder 185)
    - MacArthur, Accession no. M0245 (Box 21, Folder 186)
    - MacArthur, Accession no. M0245 (Box 21, Folder 187)
    - MacArthur, Accession no. M0245 (Box 21, Folder 188)
    - Merriam, Accession no. M0245 (Box 21, Folder 189)
    - Nixon, Accession no. M0245 (Box 21, Folder 190)
    - Nixon, Accession no. M0245 (Box 21, Folder 191)
    - Olsen, Accession no. M0245 (Box 21, Folder 192)
    - P-Q-R, Accession no. M0245 (Box 21, Folder 193)
    - Powers, Accession no. M0245 (Box 21, Folder 194)
    - Reagan, Accession no. M0245 (Box 21, Folder 195)
    - Rockefeller, N., Accession no. M0245 (Box 21, Folder 196)
    - Rockefeller, N., Accession no. M0245 (Box 21, Folder 197)
    - Rockefeller, N., Accession no. M0245 (Box 21, Folder 198)
    - R, Accession no. M0245 (Box 21, Folder 199)
    - Rolph, James A., Accession no. M0245 (Box 22, Folder 199)
    - S-T-U, Accession no. M0245 (Box 22, Folder 200)
    - Scott, J., Accession no. M0245 (Box 22, Folder 201)
    - Selassie, Accession no. M0245 (Box 22, Folder 202)
    - Shell, J. C., Accession no. M0245 (Box 22, Folder 203)
    - Thomas, Vincent, Accession no. M0245 (Box 22, Folder 204)
    - Truman, Accession no. M0245 (Box 22, Folder 205)
    - W-X-Y-Z, Accession no. M0245 (Box 22, Folder 206)
    - Warren, Accession no. M0245 (Box 22, Folder 207)
    - Warren, Accession no. M0245 (Box 22, Folder 208)
    - Whitaker t~ Baxter, Accession no. M0245 (Box 22, Folder 208)
    - Yorty, Accession no. M0245 (Box 22, Folder 209)
- Series 2. Printed Reference Material
  This series includes speeches, press releases, information cards, press conference notes, office calendars, magazines and pamphlets. SPEECHES have been listed by item, while PRESS RELEASES were given general subject listing in chronological order. PRESS CONFERENCE NOTES follow the press releases, again, in chronological order. MAGAZINES and PAMPHLETS have been kept separate from the clippings -- the former are kept alphabetically and the latter are kept by general subject heading or title.
  - Subseries 1. SPEECHES AS LIEUTENANT GOVERNOR
    - Loyalty of the Leader REMOVED TO MEMORABILIA, Accession no. M0244
    - American Peril, Then.d., Accession no. M0244 (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Cabrillo Celebration10-2-48, Accession no. M0244 (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - California Caravan Broadcast12-5-48, Accession no. M0244; 1 ditto (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - California Constitution Day9-9-47, Accession no. M0244 (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - California Manufacturer's Ass'n.: Henry Ford Luncheon2-19-47, Accession no. M0244 (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - California Manufacturer's Ass'n.: How To Cut Taxes10-5-49, Accession no. M0244; (2pp. orig. annot. and 4pp. carbon w/corrections) (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - California Safety Council1936-, Accession no. M0244; 9pp. annot. speech (9) (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - California Safety Council2-14-36 (?), Accession no. M0244; 2pp. printed pamphlet (2) (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - California Safety Council1937-, Accession no. M0244; 2pp. carbon annot. and (2) (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - California Safety Council1937, Accession no. M0244; 5pp. handwritten speech (Box 123, Folder 6)
      (5)
    - Calif. State Republican Assembly Excerpts. Note: mailed to Sadie Perlin at Sacto. airmail spec. del. 1-6-55 MDY5-16-48, Accession no. M0244; empty (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - Campaign Speeches, Accession no. M0244 (Box 123, Folder 8)
      1. No title, 4 (ta), 1946 -- 2. KSFO Radio, 12 (ta), 10-14-46 -- 3. ABC K. for Gov., 13 (ta), 10-31-46 -- 4. ABC K. for Gov., 11 (t),
      11-4-46 -- 5. A. Letter: Gladys Latham to GJK re: Capitol Car. Broadcast - Sacramento,
    - Chamber of Commerce Address by A. J. Gock What's Ahead for Southern California. (printed Pamphlet)10-5-48, Accession no. M0244 (Box 123, Folder 9)
    - Chambers of Commerce, Accession no. M0244 (Box 123, Folder 10)
      1. Agriculture and Industry, 24, 8-29-50, (printed pamphlet & memo)